Hello everyone. My name is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu.
And,
And, I'm Mina Hanane.
Yay.
Yes, so June 2nd, the day I'm taking pictures today, is Hanane Mina's birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I turned 24 years old.
Yay. Congratulations.
Yes, so today is an ordinary free talk video.
Ah, free talk.
I was wondering what's going to happen this time.
Last year, I did a project in which I kept telling Hananomi that I love her all the time,
This year, I was thinking about what to do,
But I couldn't come up with any good ideas,
I see.
Yes, something like that,
I was thinking of doing a surprise like asking the students to steal my shoelaces, or something like that,
But I couldn't come up with anything, and I thought it was too maniacal, so I decided not to do it.
So I'd like to ask Hananobi some questions in a video that is really just a free talk video.
I'm going to improvise questions now, so I don't know what kind of answers I'll get,
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Kanami, is there anything you would like to do at the age of 24?
What do you want to do?
Well, what is it?
What I want to do is...
Wait a minute. Are you okay?
What do I have in mind? What do you want to do?
What do you want to do? What about you, by the way?
Swimming? Swimming.
And I want to master cooking. Oh, that's good.
If it's cooking...
I would like to try and cook various kinds of food, Japanese and Western.
By the way, what is your best dish right now?
Well, I don't know.
But I personally like cod roe pasta.
I can make mentaiko pasta with my own favorite flavor.
Wow!
Mushroom pasta?
Yes, I do.
Looks delicious! I'm getting hungry.
I'm hungry.
Okay, second one.
Kanami, is there anything new you want to try now that you are 24 years old?
or something you would like to try in the future?
Oh, something new I want to try?
But from now on, I will be allowed to visit 10 places in Japan.
I'm going to be able to meet new people.
Yes, I think so.
Like the salted tomato daifuku from the other day.
Yes, yes, yes.
So I want to try foods that I haven't tried yet.
I don't know...
That's for sure.
Yeah, I'm on YouTube right now.
I've been learning about all kinds of things on YouTube, in all kinds of delicious groups.
I've never heard of some of them before.
Oh, yeah...
That's why...
I'm trying to
I've learned a lot of things
On the tour
I want to eat.
Knowledge.
I'll do my best to eat it on the tour.
Yes, I'll do my best next year, but
I'll do my best so that we can eat good food too.
Yes, and then there's
Ajari rice cakes.
Ajari rice cake.
Yes, I've never had it either.
They don't often appear in catered events.
But I got a lot of orders.
They said, "Ajari rice cakes are delicious!
Is that Kyoto?
Kyoto.
Kyoto?
I heard Hyogo and Kyoto are convenient.
I think it was Kyoto.
Heh~
Ajari Mochi
I'll look into it when I put in the message.
I'll check it out.
Maybe Kyoto
Kyoto
I'll look into it.I'll look into it.
Yes, and
Ms. Kanami.
Yes, sir.
Is there a country or a prefecture you would like to visit?
Country... I...
I'd like to go to Europe.
Also, I want to see the Northern Lights someday.
I talked about that in my video.
I was looking at your instagram the other day and saw the aurora borealis.
I was looking at Instagram the other day, and I saw this really beautiful aurora borealis.
Wow, I want to see that before I die.
I want to see it someday.
I'd love to see the Northern Lights.
The Aurora Borealis is amazing.
In Japan, it's not so easy.
No, I don't think Japan has auroras.
There are lots of beautiful starry skies and so on.
Aurora Borealis has a strong image from overseas.
Even now, it's hard to imagine the Aurora Borealis as a normal scenery.
I thought it was something out of a dream world.
But now that it seems to be real...
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Yes! And...
Yes, what is it?
I want to go to Albee.
And that village over there.
Of course I want to go to that village too!
Everyone in that village is so nice to me!
Happy birthday!
I've seen you on Twitter.
It's like a desert.
Desert? Africa?
Not Africa.
Oh, Tottori Sand Dunes.
Wow!
That's crazy.
Yeah.
I want to go there someday.
That's one of the things I want to do.
Yes, I do.
And you, Mr. Hanami...
If you were to change a short story to yourself for your birthday...
Is there anything you want?
Oh
What do you want?
I bought it
Actually, it's my birthday.
What did you buy?
An electric toothbrush.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Why so suddenly?
Why?
When you grow up...
Electric toothbrush.
Just like your mom used to buy you.
My brother used to get one too.
I did.
But I never got one, because I always wanted one, so I bought myself one for my brain flash.
Did you get a good one? I bought a nice one.
It's a good one. It's a good one.
It's okay. Let's go get you a new job.
That's too funny. I didn't expect that answer.
That's funny.
Okay, now... I just caught up on one more question.
Is there anyone you'd like to meet this year? Someone you'd like to collaborate with?
Really?
Maybe.
Someone I've admired for a long time... I'd like to meet Mr. Komatsuzawa.
I want to meet him!
We work in the same office.
But you don't even know each other?
No, of course not.
But I don't remember who it was, but it could have been one of the members, or the manager, or the manager...
Oh, there he is.
I've heard of him.
Is there someone at the office?
Don't go to the office.
That's not a good idea.
It would be nice to meet you on the job or something.
Really.
I'd like to meet him.
I'd like to meet you, too.
Are you recording this?
Yes, I am.
Okay, finally.
Please give a brief message to those who are watching.
Hello, everyone.
To all of you, oharu no, oharu oshi.Oharu, oharu-oshi everyone.
I'm sure many of you who are not OHARU-OSHI are also watching this.
Yes, I know.
Yes, I've been talking with Oharu about collaborating with them.
You have a plan, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm still pretty busy with work right now.
I can't do it because I'm in a rush.
I have a project that I would like to try when I have a little more free time.
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
The video has a romantic feel to it, and my favorite type of person is Kaon Tsujino.
The person I want to marry is Kaon Tsujino.
Someone sent me a message saying that his/her requirements for a girlfriend are Ms. Kaon Tsujino.
Thank you very much.
Oh, no.
I did it.
Kanamiyo is looking at it too.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so I did a lot of interviews with Kanami today.
Thank you.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
And please check out Kanami's YouTube channel.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much for watching today's video.
I'm waiting for your comments.
Please comment and say congratulations.
Thank you.
Bye bye.